[{"answer": " Where are you taking me", "docId": "It_Happened_one_night.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " that place", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " that place", "docId": "It_Happened_one_night.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "We leave that place in an hour. Soon's we get some supplies aboard", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Say, listen, you wouldn't know a story if it reached up and kicked you in the pants.  Yeah?  Sure, sure, I got your copy. Why didn't you tell me you were going to write it in Greek? I'd start a new department", "docId": "It_Happened_one_night.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " Free verse, huh?  What the dickens was free about it? It cost this paper a gob of dough. Well, I'm here to tell you, it's not gonna cost us any more", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " Free verse, huh?  What the dickens was free about it? It cost this paper a gob of dough. Well, I'm here to tell you, it's not gonna cost us any more", "docId": "It_Happened_one_night.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " When you get through with that, I'll have a beard down to my ankles.", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "It_Happened_one_night.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " Maybe they doand maybe they don't", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "That cadaverou", "docId": "It_Happened_one_night.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Don't tell me your ticket was in it", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Don't tell me your ticket was in it", "docId": "It_Happened_one_night.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "You can wire home for some money when we get to that place", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Seems to me I've already thanked you for that.  What time is the next bus to that place", "docId": "It_Happened_one_night.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Eight o'clock! Why, that's twelve hours", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " Take my advicegrab the first bus back to that place. That guy's a phony", "docId": "It_Happened_one_night.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "That's right. You didn't", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "\"Tub of mush. Well try and get it. What I said about never writing another line for you still goes. Are you burning? my friend", "docId": "It_Happened_one_night.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Collect", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Send it collect", "docId": "It_Happened_one_night.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " Collect", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Who, me?  Why, I'm the whippoorwill that cries in the night. I'm the soft morning breeze that caresses your lovely face", "docId": "It_Happened_one_night.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Yeah. I got a name. my friend", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " Where'd you say the showersand thingswere?", "docId": "It_Happened_one_night.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Where is the shower", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "that place", "docId": "It_Happened_one_night.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Oh. Is that how you met him", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Detectives", "docId": "It_Happened_one_night.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Don't look at me. I didn't marry King my friend", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": " Well, you don't have to lose your temper", "docId": "It_Happened_one_night.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "He didn't make a pass at me! I told you a million times", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " Oh, gee, my friend wouldn'tyou ain't thinkin' abou", "docId": "It_Happened_one_night.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": " SuresureI'll keep my trap shut. you can depend on me, Mister", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "It takes money to buy food", "docId": "It_Happened_one_night.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": " Not a sou. I had some before the fainting scene", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": " Not a sou. I had some before the fainting scene", "docId": "It_Happened_one_night.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I didn't give him anything . You were the bi", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "I didn't give him anything . You were the bi", "docId": "It_Happened_one_night.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": " Must be some strange power my friend has over you women.  How do you expect to get there", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": " Sorry.  It's the first time I've ridden", "docId": "It_Happened_one_night.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Of course it is", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "I wish you wouldn't talk too much. We let a car get away.", "docId": "It_Happened_one_night.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Oh, they'll stop, all right. It's a matter of knowing how to hail them", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "It_Happened_one_night.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": " Well, you got one now. Come on, fill 'er up", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Husband", "docId": "It_Happened_one_night.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Isn't he here", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "You're a peculiar chap", "docId": "It_Happened_one_night.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "The average man would go after the reward. All you seem t", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "The average man would go after the reward. All you seem t", "docId": "It_Happened_one_night.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "You were taken for a buggy ride", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": " A normal human being couldn't live under the same roof with her, without going nuts.  She's my idea of nothing", "docId": "It_Happened_one_night.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": " Yes!  But don't hold that against me. I'm a little screwy myself", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "What do you reckon that's for", "docId": "It_Happened_one_night.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": " A trumpet", "qsentId": 56}]